Prayer Line at the South Korea Crusade
With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 2
I have a slipped disc - L3, L4, L5 and L6 are all damaged
and are pressing on my nerves, causing my legs to become paralysed.
I have numbness in my back, down to my feet.
I can't walk. My feet are in pain.
Healing In Jesus' Name
Amen!
Healing in Jesus' name.
Put it down!
Healing In Jesus' Name
Healed In the Name of Jesus
Hallelujah!
Praise God! Glory be to God!
Healed In Jesus' Name
Hallelujah!
The South Korea Crusade
With Prophet T.B. Joshua Day 2
Pastor, please help me!
I had an operation and now, I am bleeding!
It couldn't work on me! Please heal me!
Man of God, please, help me! I cannot walk and I have been bleeding for the last five months.
It doesn't stop! Please, help me to stop the bleeding!
Please help me!
Healing In Jesus' Name
Healed In Jesus' Name
Thank You, Jesus! Hallelujah!
I could not walk before but now, I can walk!
Thank You, Jesus!
Healed In Jesus' Name
South Korea Crusade With T.B. Joshua
Testimony continues
Testimony From The South Korea Crusade
With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 2
I glorify the name of Jesus.
She is my wife
Lee Jae Kweon
Chung Nam, South Korea
My name is Lee Jae Kweon. I am from Chung Nam, South Korea. The woman beside me is my wife.
I had a slipped disc. I came to the crusade with crutches
and my wife came in a wheelchair.
After receiving prayer from Prophet T.B. Joshua, we are completely healed.
Now, I am able to walk without crutches
and my wife can walk without the need of a wheelchair.
I came to the crusade with crutches because of spinal stenosis
and my wife came to the crusade in a wheelchair.
After receiving prayer from Prophet T.B. Joshua, we are both totally healed and now we are free.
Testimony From The South Korea Crusade
With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 2
The man standing next to me is my husband.
My name is Kim Yeon Ok and the man standing next to me is my husband.
I came to the crusade in a wheelchair and my husband came with crutches.
Now, we are completely healed and healthy. So we are very thankful to God.
We are very happy because we received freedom. We give glory and thanksgiving to God.
I came to the crusade in a wheelchair and my husband came with crutches.
But now, both of us are completely healed. I am very thankful to God. I am very free now.
I really thank God for this healing and miracles.
Thank You, God! You gave us freedom and healing.
Our Lord, Jesus, we love You!
Thank You, God. I love You, Jesus, for freeing me!
Testimony From The South Korea Crusade
With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 2
TT: Esther Mwelwa, 21/9/2018
RV: Mel Flowers 16/11/2018